Hi and welcome to this new video. I'm going to show you what I bought from
Dollskill and Badinka. So it's going to be a haul and try on and have fun
watching me dressing in weird things. I bought all the items with my own money
and nobody paid me to do this video. While I was surfing around the internet
I stumbled upon the page of Dollskill. I never heard of them before but I had to buy some clothes.
Their clothing? It's hard to pronounce clothes in German. I did not have a lucky hand with all of
them but I'm going to show you. Alright this is a cute skirt with some PVC, some
mesh, is it mesh? It has holes, really small holes and some metal rings. It's a
skater style skirt which I really like because I think it is nice on my figure
I don't know. I really like the cut of the skirt. I think it falls nice although
I have to watch out if I'm going to wear it to cover this upper part because
somehow it doesn't look too good if you see every part. I don't know maybe I have
to wear some long corset or something like that.
This is a biker style faux leather dress.
There is a belt and there are some red racing stripes on each side of the dress.
The straps are made of polyester weaving with these funny plastic buckles which you know
from backpacks and stuff like that.
And it has a zipper all the way to the bottom so it's I guess pretty easy to dress.
I think it has a nice fit and it's a different style than the one I usually go for.
So this was definitely a good pick.
This little plastic waist belt thingy was the cheapest item I bought.
was about $14 and it came to me with a hole on one of the bonings. The seam detached from
the plastic and it doesn't fit really well. It's too small. Definitely not the best pick.
I had to buy these pants because they looked so strange and I thought I have
to like feel them and touch them to know how they feel. They have some really long
ribbons on the side of each leg which looks a bit weird when you pull them up
while you wear it so maybe I'll have to cut them but they're super comfy they
are super lightweight so obviously you can wear them for sports or just to lay
on the couch I'm definitely going to do another sporty goth photo shooting with
these funny pants and if you want to see the results check out my Instagram so
Yeah, I think they're funny.
This funny is... oh, this is funny.
This jacket is so spacey.
I saw it and I was like, this is super weird and I can't imagine me wearing this.
So I bought it nevertheless to see me wearing this.
I don't know, it doesn't make any sense.
Anyway this was the most expensive piece of the things I bought at Dollskill.
It cost 20, no it cost 42 dollars still on sale.
And I really like all the details, all the weird dots, silver whatever parts and it makes
funny noises and I never thought it would look cool but I'm really happy that I tried
it and I think I'm going to use it for photo shootings mainly because I guess I
won't really wear it when I go out because it's a bit too fancy.
The second part of this haul is about the two items I bought at Barinka.
They're doing printed lycra jumpsuits and bodysuits and the first one I bought is this
golden jumpsuit. It's not printed so it's not their typical style but it's made of thousands
of tiny dots, golden dots, no sleeves and a big cutout in the back and a cool hood.
And I already did some photoshoots with this one.
I think it looks really cool.
And since I realized that I'm more of a golden color type person, I don't know, I thought
I give this one a try.
There's even a print in the hood I just saw.
I'm not going to wear this at a festival I guess because it's too bright for the goth
festivals.
attend to but I'm going to wear it at shootings and maybe for some fun night
out with friends in the summer. Second jumpsuit I bought is a jumpsuit with a
lot of eyes and a bit creepy I don't know it feels like I have multiple eyes
no no it has long arms and long legs and some different colored eyes in the hood
and this is so funny I thought when I saw this about sitting at a festival in
the morning like waking up going out of the tent sitting down when everyone is
half asleep and wearing this funny suit. But I can also wear it just in this
video now or at a couch I don't mind because it's really comfy. It has some
finger loop hole thingies and which is great in this jumpsuit because normally
the arms are too short for me to put my thumbs through these holes but here it's
a great size it's a great length and it's a fitted onesie so it's tight but
still comfy and yeah I really like it I think it looks really fun and cool and
it has a cool hood
So that was it. Thanks for watching. Leave a comment if you like and tell me what
your favorite outfit was or if you ever bought something at Dollskill or
and subscribe to my channel. Thanks and bye!